http://www.senacases.com/pages/privacy-policy#accessibility

GET 2-DAY USA SHIPPING FOR $5 ON ORDERS $49+
Login
Register
Contact Us
Searchbox for desktop_search:
Shopping Cart
My Cart (0)
Close Dropdown Cart
No products in the cart.
Total:
Checkout
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
Searchbox for sticky_search:
Search Privacy Policy | SENA Cases
Search
Visit breadcrumb, position 1, link to SENA Cases
Privacy Policy
We care about your privacy!
This Privacy Policy describes and informs you of SENA’s (sometimes referred to as “us,” “we,” or “our”) online information collection, use, and disclosure practices and your choices regarding the collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to all information, including personal data, collected from the SenaCases.com website and also applies to certain other electronic information as outlined below. You consent to and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy by using our website.
The Personal Data We Collect About You
We collect personal data that you voluntarily provide to us on this website, such as your email address, billing and shipping address, name, organization, title, telephone number, credit card number and other payment information, demographic information, or persistent identifier (such as your username and password). In addition, when you visit our website, our web server automatically recognizes and stores your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (the Internet address of your computer or device). Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you have activated blocking technology available in some browsers.
The Reason Why We Collect Your Personal Data
The personal data that we collect on this website help us address your needs and provide services to you. The personal data that you provide to us enable you to make a purchase on our website, register for a webinar, register a product or submit a warranty claim, communicate with us, enter into sweepstakes, participate in an online survey, provide product reviews, subscribe to a mailing list or newsletter, or register for special purchase discounts. The personal data that we automatically collect from your computer and device, such as your IP address, help us determine which areas of our website are being visited and the length of the visit. This information helps us better understand our visitors, tailor our visitors’ experience on this website, and improve the website.
Whether We Share Your Personal Data With Others
We do not sell your personal data to third parties. We do, however, share your personal data with service providers who assist us in providing services on this website. This includes, for example, providing your personal data to service providers who help process and ship your orders, communicate with you, and screen orders for potential risk or fraud.
Further, we use a service provider, Google Analytics, to help us understand how our customers use this website. You can read more about how Google Analytics uses your information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Lastly, we may share your personal data if necessary to: (1) comply with foreign or domestic laws; (2) comply with a civil, criminal, or regulatory inquiry, investigation, subpoena, or summons by foreign or domestic authorities; (3) cooperate with law enforcement agencies concerning conduct or activity that we reasonably and in good faith believe may violate foreign or domestic laws; or (4) exercise or defend legal claims.
How We Protect Your Personal Data
We have implemented and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices, and commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures, to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk in order to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access and exfiltration, theft, or disclosure. We are committed to protecting your personal data, but you can do your part. You should create a strong password and protect against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and do not share your password with anyone. We cannot guarantee the security of any personal data you transmit to us, and by using our website and services you acknowledge this risk. We will notify you if there is a breach of our security where required by law or deemed necessary.
Retention of Personal Data
Your personal data will be retained for the time required to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and processed, including for the purpose of satisfying legal, professional, contractual, regulatory, accounting or reporting obligations.
Children
Our website and services are not intended for or directed at children under the age of 13. In addition, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.
Cookies
Like many websites today, we may employ a standard technology called “cookies” to collect information about how you use our site in order to provide you with a better experience by measuring which areas of our website of greatest interest or to remember you when you return to visit us. SENA uses cookies to deliver improved functionality and to enhance your experience on our websites. We also use cookies and similar technologies in some emails. These email cookies help us to understand whether recipients have opened an email and how they have interacted with it. If you have enabled images, cookies may be set on your computer or device. Cookies may also be activated if you click on links within emails.
Subject to your right to reject cookies and delete them as described below, your use of our website and services indicates that you accept our Cookies policy.
What are cookies?
A cookie is a small piece of data that a website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device. The cookie allows the website to “remember” your actions or preferences over time. Most browsers support cookies, but users can set their browsers to decline them and can delete them whenever they like. Websites mainly use cookies to identify users, remember users’ custom preferences, and help users complete tasks without having to re enter information when browsing from one page to another or when visiting the website later. Cookies can also be used for online target advertising and to show advertisements relevant to something the user searched for in the past.
The web server supplying the webpage can store a cookie on the user’s computer or mobile device. An external web server that manages files included or referenced in the webpage is also able to store cookies. Each time the user requests a new page, the web server can receive the value of the cookies it previously set and return the page with content relating to these values.
What are the different types of cookies?
A cookie can be classified by its lifespan and the domain to which it belongs. By lifespan, cookies are either:
a session cookie, which is erased when the user closes the browser; this type of cookie is used, for instance, as a test to see whether or not browser settings allow cookies to be set on your machine; or
a persistent cookie, which remains on the user's computer/device for a defined period of time. These types of cookies enable the platform to remember a visitor and to serve users with appropriate content while speeding up the load rate of the web page.
As for the domain to which it belongs, cookies are either:
first-party cookies, which are set by the web server of the visited page and share the same domain; or
third-party cookies, stored by a different domain to the visited page's domain. This can happen when the webpage references a file, such as JavaScript, located outside its domain.
How to control and delete cookies
If you want to restrict or block the cookies, you can do so in your browser settings. The ‘help’ function within your browser should generally tell you how. The website www.aboutcookies.org also contains general information on cookies on a wide variety of browsers. That website describes how to delete cookies from your computer.
If you do not want to accept cookies from our emails, simply close the email before downloading any images or clicking on any links. You can also set your browser to restrict or reject cookies. These settings will apply to all cookies on websites and emails. In some instances, depending on your email or browser settings, cookies in an email may be automatically accepted (for example, if you have added an email address to your address book or safe senders list). Please check your email browser or device instructions for more information on this.
Behavioral advertising
We use your information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Twitter: https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/62931/manage-advertising-preferences?lang=en
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
European Residents
If you are a resident of Europe, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information on this website.
Additionally, if you are a resident of Europe we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example, if you make an order of a product listed on this website), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.
Do Not Track Notice
This website does not currently support certain browser settings or otherwise respond to Do Not Track requests. You can find out more information about opting-out of interest-based advertising at: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.
Linked Websites
Other sites which are linked to/from our website (including the websites of SENA affiliates) may have different policies. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those sites for details.
Our Commitment to Accessibility:
SENA is committed to making our website's content accessible and user friendly to everyone. If you are having difficulty viewing or navigating the content on this website, or notice any content, feature, or functionality that you believe is not fully accessible to people with disabilities, please call our Customer Service team at (877) 482-7487 or email our team at ADAAssist@senacases.com, include “Disabled Access” in the subject line and provide a description of the specific feature you feel is not fully accessible or a suggestion for improvement. We take your feedback seriously and will consider it as we evaluate ways to accommodate all of our customers and our overall accessibility policies. Additionally, while we do not control such vendors, we strongly encourage vendors of third-party digital content to provide content that is accessible and user friendly.
NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
Beginning January 1, 2020, California residents may exercise certain privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) regarding their “personal information,” which is defined under the CCPA to mean information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household. We describe below your rights if you are a California resident.
Right To Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold
We generally describe in this privacy policy how we collect, use, and share your personal information. In addition to what is described above, as a California resident, you also have the right to request more information regarding the following topics for the preceding 12 months, to the extent applicable:
The categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
The categories of sources from which we have collected your personal information.
The business or commercial purpose why we collected or, if applicable, sold your personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we shared your personal information.
The categories of personal information that we have shared with third parties about you for a business purpose.
If applicable, the categories of personal information that we sold about you and the categories of third parties who received your personal information in the sale.
You may submit a request for the information above by calling us at (877) 482-7487 or complete our CCPA Inquiry Form. Once you contact us through one of these channels, we will need to confirm your identity to process your request.
Right To Request Deletion Of Your Personal Information
You have the right to request that we delete the personal information we collected or maintained about you. Once we receive your request, we will let you know what, if any, personal information we can delete from our records, and we will direct any service providers with whom we shared your personal information to also delete your personal information from their records.
There may be circumstances where we cannot delete your personal information or direct service providers to delete your personal information from their records. Some of these instances include, but are not limited to, if we need to: (1) retain your personal information to complete a transaction or provide a good or service; (2) detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for that activity; (3) debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality; (4) exercise free speech or ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right to free speech; (5) comply with the law; and (6) use your personal information for internal and lawful purposes.
You may submit a request to delete your personal information by calling us at (877) 482-7487 or complete our CCPA Inquiry Form. Once you contact us through one of these channels, we will need to confirm your identity to process your request.
Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information
We do not and will not sell your personal information to third parties. As such, there is no need to submit a request for us to not sell your personal information. If you have any questions, feel free to contact us at (877) 482-7487 or US.Privacy@senacases.com.
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Your Privacy Rights
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights under the CCPA, as described above. This includes, but is not limited to: (A) denying good or services to you; (B) charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties; (C) providing a different level or quality of goods or services; or (D) suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Authorized Agent
You may use an authorized agent to submit requests on your behalf to exercise the rights above.
Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at US.Privacy@senacases.com or (877) 482-7487.
Added to cart successfully!
Qty:
Price:
There are 0 itemsin your cart
Total:
successfully!
People Who Bought This Also Bought
Price:
